這位行者
我們這一支香就
修最純淨的一支香
都不加減
我們就一直修下去
隨頌起觀
尤其持咒的時候
盡量地用整個感覺
融入去念它
有時候開示會分心
每一句你都要掌握到
我在過程裡面
最後一句會加重
會有點放慢
然後就是又到下面
另外一個輪
我們就開始來修前行
奧義大罵亦都
不拉巴哇亦都
得心大大噶都
哈曰哇地
得心
才有
尼羅大
亦往
巴地
馬哈
斯拉
馬拉
耶
斯哇
哈
奧義大罵亦都
不拉巴哇亦都
得心
大大噶都
哈曰哇地
得心
才有
尼羅大
亦往
巴地
馬哈
斯拉
馬拉
耶
斯哇
哈
奧義大罵亦都
不拉巴哇亦都
得心
大大噶都
哈曰哇地
得心
才有
尼羅大
亦往
巴地
馬哈
斯拉
馬拉
耶
斯哇
哈
南巴南
遮
大巴
大巴
首等詞
Om Svabhavastu
Dharma Svabhavastu
Hum
一切法空
於自性空中
顯現密言察圖
月亮宮內
八獅子座
蓮花日月輪
中有阿字
放光
隨機收射
順成本尊
觀想自己
變成本尊
從眉心這邊開始觀想
首先你可以觀想眉心
它是一個明點
放著光
然後往上
頭顱
天庭飽滿
頭顱圓坨坨
可以觀想
右弦的法器
也可以觀想
戴五方佛冠
然後再往下
往左右觀想
眉毛修長
眼睛澄澈分明
鼻子堅挺有肉
嘴巴紅潤
嘴角帶著微笑
下巴
臉頰
耳朵垂肩
頸
肩
上手臂
下手臂
兩手輕輕放胸前
結印
再往下觀想
胸
背
腹
腰
臀腿
頸
兩足金剛
加輔作
披三法衣
合掌
引請智慧尊降臨融入
吾法吉拉撒瑪扎
扎
弘
王
智慧尊住於心間蓮花月輪上
觀想身體中央有中脈
頂輪白色光點
喉輪紅色
心輪藍色
脊輪黃色
蜜輪綠色
它是我們撐 彈 吃 慢 記 五毒所系
藉著譬如真老婆的大罐頂光真言
把它照透
把它去除
也順著我們的觀想詞咒
將它化入虛空
首先把注意力集中在頂輪
順次往下
弘
王
折
弘
在你的脊輪觀想一下
那個地方有一種灼熱的感覺
那個亮
越集中越好
在那邊戰 戰 戰鬥
就好像
那個電爐
電爐的爐瓷
透亮 熱
放著光在那個地方
當然我們觀想一點就可以了
接著到心輪
弘
光就代表智慧
接著我們把這個觀想起來
意所生的
意是也是一樣
意所生就本來沒有
透過我們的意念的觀想顯現
那這邊也透過我們的意念的觀想
然後融入空
還是回歸空
所以我們用最恭敬、清淨、喜悅的心
上公、十方諸佛
下師六道有情
呼
整個融掉
把我們所結的印也放開
上面的腳就放到下面去
另外那個腳就往外攤
往下踩
手輕輕的覆蓋在膝蓋上
腰微微往前挺
抬頭挺胸
頭微仰
閉著眼睛
將那個看透過你的慧眼
就眉心
從遠處看
其實有時候你一這樣做
馬上那個湛藍色的明點就出現
其實應該還蠻親切的
你就輕輕的看著這個湛藍色的明點
不作意
但是只是觀察
看著它的變化
耳朵就聽
只是聽
不取捨、不分別
心保持覺照
沒有冷鎖
就好像水晶珠
水晶周遭的東西都涉入在裡面
不知不覺
了了分明
心保持覺照
沒有冷鎖
不取捨
不分別
有時候你會感覺到
有些東西會出現在你眼睛裡
有些東西會出在你眼睛裡
【Observations to believe this story was to be believed at some time in 40BCUT】
【Observations to believe this story was to be believed in 40BCUT】
【Observations to be believed in 40BCUT】
【Observations to believe this story was to be believed in 40B CUT】
【Observations to believe this story was to be believed in 40BCUT】
This one is to maintain a state of stillness.
Slowly, all the tension in your body
will slowly dissipate in this state.
The flow of consciousness
will also seem to be still in this state.
In the whole of the Dharma world,
only the last one is clear.
Everything else is just a clear state of stillness.
It becomes a thing,
not a relative thing.
If there is any sound,
you will feel that sound
as if it can penetrate your fake body.
Slowly, we will be able to
let go of the physical and
the obstacles in our body.
We will no longer care about them.
We will no longer cling to them.
When we no longer cling to them,
and no longer care about them,
our body will no longer be tense.
Everything will seem to be clear.
When your mind is completely clear,
your body will be in this state of emptiness and stillness.
Slowly, even if you are sick,
you will slowly recover.
You must believe in the freedom of the Dharma world.
You must also believe in the energy of emptiness and stillness.
In fact, these fake diseases arising from causes and conditions,
as long as you have a strong understanding of them,
they can still be resolved.
Whether they can be resolved,
depends on how well you understand them.
This has nothing to do with superstition.
Once you believe in them,
you will be able to develop your strength.
If you don't believe in them,
it is best to seek a doctor.
It is best to seek a doctor.
However, a doctor may not be able to cure you.
Unless you break through your karma,
the disease will not be serious.
Now, let's practice meditation.
When walking, it is the same.
Each step, use a little bit of light force.
Lift your feet up a little bit, and put them down.
Use your strength to vibrate them.
You can also vibrate away all the bad qi in your body.